GAGANDEEP SINGH BHUI

Address: 1003, Tower O, Grand Ajnara Heritage, Sector 74

Gautam Budh Nagar (NOIDA), Uttar Pradesh - 201306, INDIA

Phone: +91 87-2507-0727

E-mail: gagandeep.bhui@gmail.com



Key Skills

New Business Development

Strategic Planning

OperationsManagement

Key Account Management

Customer Relationship

Management

Staff Training &

Development

Contract Negotiations

Budgeting & Forecasting

Driven professional with 8+ years of experience in B2B Sales/ New Business Development/ Customer Relationship Management. With exceptional communication and leadership skills, has a record of selling luxury experiences to Corporate, NGO's and Associations.

Possess strong strategic prospecting of new customers, great rapport building and negotiation skills. A goal-oriented professional has experience in working for the best brands across the industry that is Carlson Group of Hotels, Hyatt Hotels Corporation & Taj Hotels.

Work Experiences

- **♣ Sales Manager at jüSTa Hotels & Resorts** (part of Onora Hospitality Private Limited) from April 2019 to March 2020
 - Managed strategic accounts (Corporate, NGO's & Associations).
 - Actively involved in cold calling & regular visits to procure new business for the organisation.
 - O Built multiple relationships across different levels administration, procurement until country heads.
 - Conducted site visits to prospective clients.
 - Acquired, retained & developed accounts to improve market share both in terms of groups & transient business.
 - Coordinated with other hotel-level departments to facilitate services agreed upon by the sales office and prospective clients.
 - Executed hotel-level tactical sales and marketing plans to support overall system-wide sales plans/strategies and programs.
 - Actively recognizing and capitalizing on market trends & competitor activity.
- Corporate Alliance Manager at OYO Rooms (part of Oravel Stays Private Limited) from April 2018 to April 2019
 - O Identification of new prospective clients, nurturing old clients for retention of business.
 - During tenure, provided 15% increase in new business to OYO every quarter.
 - Regular coordination day & night with clients to provide best of facilities to the client.

- **♣ Sales Manager at 221b Baker Street** (part of The Trinity Corporation) from March 2017 to March 2018
 - O Looked after Territory Sales and facilitated with Star Performer of the Quarter
 - Developed incremental business through active prospecting, referrals and leads.
 - Reporting and reviewing of monthly, quarterly, and year-end sales
- ♣ Assistant Manager (Operations) at WWICS Global Law Offices Pvt. Ltd. Head Office {Mohali} from April 2016 to March 2017
 - O Documentation, Verification, Tracking and Reporting of case files of the organization
 - O Maintaining internal daily, weekly and monthly reports
 - Monitor cases and track deadlines of the case records
- **Assistant Sales Manager at TAJ Chandigarh** (part of The Indian Hotels Company Limited) from June 2015 to January 2016
 - **O** Developed and maintained relationships with key clients in order to produce group and/or convention business, including room sales, food & beverage sales, catering/banquet services.
 - Coordinated with other hotel-level departments to facilitate services agreed upon by the sales office and prospective clients.
 - Executed hotel-level tactical sales and marketing plans to support overall system-wide sales plans/strategies and programs.
- ♣ Sales Manager at Hyatt Hyderabad Gachibowli from July 2011 till April 2014
 - O ISTA Hotels underwent a management change-over and got re-branded to Hyatt Hotels Corporation W.E.F. 01 April 2013.
 - Solicited, negotiated and confirmed new and repeat business; while meeting deadlines and responding to corporate sales leads in a timely manner.
 - Set sales goal for group bookings, corporate accounts, new leads, contacts etc.
 - Finalization of contracts for bookings.

Educational Qualifications:

3-year Higher Diploma in Hospitality & Management (2007 – 2010) from RIG Institute of Hospitality & Management, Greater Noida – Uttar Pradesh affiliated to HTMi Switzerland.

Certifications & Trainings:

- Supply Chain Fundamentals: Understanding the Basics (Udemy) 17 April 2020
- Management Associate at Radisson Suites, Gurgaon (part of Carlson Group of Hotels) from June 2010 to June 2011
- Industrial Trainee at The Taj Mahal Hotel, New Delhi (part of The Indian Hotels Company Limited) from July 2008 to Nov 2008

Personal Information:

Date of Birth: 07.07.1989Marital Status: Married

O Languages Known: English, Hindi and Punjabi